https://www.databasedads.com/privacy-policy

Data Based Ads' Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to https://www.databasedads.com and Data Based Ads, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Data Based Ads, Inc. include https://www.databasedads.com and DBA. The DBA website is a marketing site. By using the DBA website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
DBA does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
DBA may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to DBA, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
DBA may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on DBA or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of DBA; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of DBA, or the public.
Automatically Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by DBA. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the DBA website.
Use of Cookies
The DBA website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize DBA pages, or register with DBA site or services, a cookie helps DBA to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same DBA website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the DBA features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the DBA services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
DBA secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. DBA uses the SSL Protocol for this purpose:
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.
Children Under Thirteen
DBA does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
E-mail Communications
From time to time, DBA may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from DBA or click on a link therein.
If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from DBA, you may opt out of such communications by clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE button or link..
Changes to this Statement
DBA reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
Contact Information
DBA welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that DBA has not adhered to this Statement, please contact DBA at:
Data Based Ads, Inc.661 W Lake St, 1SChicago, Illinois 60661
Email Address:security@databasedads.com
Telephone number:(312) 280-9780
Effective as of December 01, 2019
About Data Based Ads, Inc.
Data Based Ads, Inc. is a real estate software developer serving brokerage and media company clients of all sizes with print and online real estate advertising and data management through its proprietary web-based, multi-level software-as-a-service solutions.
Learn More [fa icon="long-arrow-right"]
[fa icon="home"] 661 West Lake St, Ste 1S, Chicago, IL 60661
[fa icon="facebook-square"] [fa icon="linkedin-square"] [fa icon="twitter-square"]
Copyright 2020 Data Based Ads, Inc.. All rights reserved.
[fa icon="chevron-up"]
